<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<modDesc descVersion="73">
    <author>Luke Bradbury</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>LFHA ForageOptima Standard</en>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Forage Optima tweaks certain gameplay elements to make Forage Harvesters more worthwhile. Some equipment is improved, but the main focus is improved chaff yield.

Introducing the LFHA ForageOptima Standard: A Game-Changing Set of Guidelines for Forage Harvesting

Lizard Forage Harvesting Association (LFHA), a renowned industry body specializing in forage harvesting technology and innovation, proudly announces the LFHA ForageOptima Standard. This groundbreaking set of guidelines significantly enhances forage harvesting operations, primarily through improved grass and corn management practices.

The LFHA ForageOptima Standard brings revolutionary advancements to the industry by incorporating the latest research findings and market trends, resulting in a more realistic and efficient forage harvesting experience. Key components of the standard include:

  1. LFHA proudly certifies pickup headers for efficient hay foraging, opening up new opportunities for farmers to streamline their hay production process.
  2. Thanks to innovative technology, hay collected by forage harvesters experiences reduced pickup losses, ensuring a more efficient and productive harvesting operation.
  3. Groundbreaking advancements in direct cutter header design have received LFHA's seal of approval for closer cutting capabilities, now slightly surpassing traditional mowers in performance and precision.
  4. Significant advancements in corn yields, resulting from breakthroughs in corn hybrid varieties and agronomic techniques, increasing chaff production.
  5. Optimized forage harvesting performance, as corn silage production now surpasses grass during the summer months, thanks to cutting-edge research and market insights.

As a leading authority in the forage harvesting industry, LFHA is committed to delivering the most innovative and effective solutions for today's farming professionals. The LFHA ForageOptima Standard is a testament to our dedication to supporting the farming community with advanced guidelines that enhance productivity and sustainability.

To experience the benefits of the LFHA ForageOptima Standard, implement these guidelines into your forage harvesting operations. Unleash the full potential of your forage harvesting with LFHA's ForageOptima Standard.

For more information about LFHA and our mission to revolutionize forage harvesting technology, please visit https://github.com/hansnqyr/FS22_ForageOptima

About Lizard Forage Harvesting Association (LFHA)

LFHA is a pioneering organization focused on promoting innovation and best practices in the field of forage harvesting. Our commitment to research and development, combined with our extensive industry knowledge, enables us to deliver groundbreaking solutions that enhance farming productivity and sustainability. The LFHA ForageOptima Standard is one of our latest offerings designed to empower farmers with cutting-edge guidelines for efficient and productive forage harvesting experiences.
]]></en>
		<de><![CDATA[Forage Optima optimiert bestimmte Gameplay-Elemente, um Forage Harvesters lohnender zu machen. Einige Geräte wurden verbessert, aber das Hauptaugenmerk liegt auf einer verbesserten Spreuausbeute.

Einführung des LFHA ForageOptima Standards: Ein bahnbrechender Satz von Richtlinien für die Futterernte

Lizard Forage Harvesting Association (LFHA), ein renommierter Branchenverband, der sich auf Futtererntetechnologie und -innovation spezialisiert hat, gibt stolz den LFHA ForageOptima Standard bekannt. Diese bahnbrechenden Richtlinien verbessern die Futterernte erheblich, hauptsächlich durch verbesserte Gras- und Maismanagementpraktiken.

Der LFHA ForageOptima Standard bringt revolutionäre Fortschritte in die Branche, indem er die neuesten Forschungsergebnisse und Markttrends einbezieht, was zu einem realistischeren und effizienteren Futterernteerlebnis führt. Zu den wichtigsten Komponenten des Standards gehören:

  1. Die LFHA zertifiziert stolz Pick-up-Schneidwerke für eine effiziente Heusuche und eröffnet den Landwirten neue Möglichkeiten, ihren Heuproduktionsprozess zu rationalisieren.
  2. Dank innovativer Technologie erfährt das von Feldhäckslern gesammelte Heu weniger Aufnahmeverluste, was einen effizienteren und produktiveren Erntebetrieb gewährleistet.
  3. Bahnbrechende Fortschritte bei der Konstruktion von Direktschneidwerken haben das LFHA-Gütesiegel für engere Schneidfähigkeiten erhalten und übertreffen jetzt leicht herkömmliche Mäher in Leistung und Präzision.
  4. Bedeutende Fortschritte bei den Maiserträgen, resultierend aus Durchbrüchen bei Mais-Hybridsorten und agronomischen Techniken, wodurch die Spreuproduktion gesteigert wird.
  5. Optimierte Leistung bei der Futterernte, da die Maissilageproduktion jetzt dank modernster Forschung und Marktkenntnisse in den Sommermonaten Gras übertrifft.

Als führende Autorität in der Futtererntebranche ist LFHA bestrebt, die innovativsten und effektivsten Lösungen für die Landwirte von heute zu liefern. Der LFHA ForageOptima Standard ist ein Beweis für unser Engagement, die landwirtschaftliche Gemeinschaft mit fortschrittlichen Richtlinien zu unterstützen, die Produktivität und Nachhaltigkeit verbessern.

Um die Vorteile des LFHA ForageOptima Standards zu erleben, implementieren Sie diese Richtlinien in Ihren Futtererntebetrieb. Schöpfen Sie mit dem ForageOptima Standard von LFHA das volle Potenzial Ihrer Futterernte aus.

Weitere Informationen über LFHA und unsere Mission, die Futtererntetechnologie zu revolutionieren, finden Sie unter https://github.com/hansnqyr/FS22_ForageOptima

Über die Lizard Forage Harvesting Association (LFHA)

LFHA ist eine wegweisende Organisation, die sich auf die Förderung von Innovationen und Best Practices im Bereich der Futterernte konzentriert. Unser Engagement für Forschung und Entwicklung, kombiniert mit unserem umfassenden Branchenwissen, ermöglicht es uns, bahnbrechende Lösungen zu liefern, die die landwirtschaftliche Produktivität und Nachhaltigkeit verbessern. Der LFHA ForageOptima Standard ist eines unserer neuesten Angebote, das entwickelt wurde, um Landwirte mit modernsten Richtlinien für eine effiziente und produktive Futterernte zu unterstützen.
]]></de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_ForageOptima.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="ForageOptima.lua"/>
    </extraSourceFiles>
</modDesc>
